(Sheldon:)Mom, you remember Rajesh?
Rajesh, my mother.
(Raj:)Of course. Mrs. Cooper.
So nice to see you again.
Well, it's so nice to see you too. Heh.
(Mrs Cooper:)I thought it was our Indians
that had the occasional alcohol problem.
(Leonard:)We don't say that, either.
(Leonard:)I'll make you a list.
(Mrs Cooper:)Oh, that would be
mighty white of you.
(Mrs Cooper:)So, Raj, what pain
are you trying to cover up...
(Mrs Cooper:)...with alcohol?
- Nothing, I'm fine.
- Are you?
(Mrs Cooper:)No.
(Mrs Cooper:)That's better.
Now, tell me what's bothering you.
I'm so Ionely.
(Sheldon:)Oh, yes, born alone, die alone.
It's a tragic human condition.
(Sheldon:)Now, Raj,
if you'll excuse my mother...
(Sheldon:)...she's about to make a pecan pie
that'll be so good...
(Sheldon:)...I'll almost forget how she blew it
with the fried chicken.
Sheldon, your friend is hurting.